<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Covid-19</title>
    <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid</link>
    <atom:link href="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/reports.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <description>Temporal variation in transmission during the COVID-19 outbreak
</description>
    <generator>Distill</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Global summary</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Global summary</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="10800" height="3600"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Afghanistan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Afghanistan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Albania</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/albania</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Albania. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/albania</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/albania/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Curaçao</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/curaçao</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Curaçao. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/curaçao</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/curaçao/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cyprus</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/cyprus</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cyprus. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/cyprus</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/cyprus/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Czechia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/czechia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Czechia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/czechia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/czechia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Denmark</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/denmark</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Denmark. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/denmark</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/denmark/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Djibouti</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/djibouti</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Djibouti. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/djibouti</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/djibouti/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dominica</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominica</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dominica. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominica</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominica/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dominican Republic</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominican-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dominican Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominican-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/dominican-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Ecuador</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/ecuador</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Ecuador. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/ecuador</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/ecuador/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Egypt</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/egypt</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Egypt. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/egypt</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/egypt/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for El Salvador</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/el-salvador</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in El Salvador. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/el-salvador</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/el-salvador/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Equatorial Guinea</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/equatorial-guinea</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Equatorial Guinea. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/equatorial-guinea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/equatorial-guinea/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Eritrea</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/eritrea</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Eritrea. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/eritrea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/eritrea/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Estonia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/estonia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Estonia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/estonia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/estonia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Japan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/japan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Japan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/japan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/japan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Jersey</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jersey</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Jersey. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jersey</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jersey/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Jordan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jordan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Jordan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jordan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/jordan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kazakhstan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kazakhstan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kazakhstan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kazakhstan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kazakhstan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kenya</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kenya</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kenya. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kenya</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kenya/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kosovo</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kosovo</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kosovo. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kosovo</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kosovo/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kuwait</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kuwait</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kuwait. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kuwait</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kuwait/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kyrgyzstan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kyrgyzstan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kyrgyzstan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kyrgyzstan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/kyrgyzstan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Laos</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/laos</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Laos. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/laos</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/laos/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Paraguay</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/paraguay</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Paraguay. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/paraguay</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/paraguay/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Peru</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/peru</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Peru. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/peru</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/peru/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Philippines</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/philippines</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Philippines. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/philippines</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/philippines/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Poland</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/poland</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Poland. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/poland</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/poland/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Portugal</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/portugal</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Portugal. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/portugal</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/portugal/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/puerto-rico</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Puerto Rico. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/puerto-rico</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/puerto-rico/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Qatar</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/qatar</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Qatar. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/qatar</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/qatar/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Réunion</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/réunion</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Réunion. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/réunion</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/réunion/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Romania</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/romania</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Romania. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/romania</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/romania/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Russia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Russia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Rwanda</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/rwanda</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Rwanda. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/rwanda</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/rwanda/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Saint Martin (French part)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saint-martin--french-part-</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Saint Martin (French part). These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saint-martin--french-part-</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saint-martin--french-part-/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for San Marino</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/san-marino</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in San Marino. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/san-marino</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/san-marino/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Saudi Arabia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Saudi Arabia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saudi-arabia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/saudi-arabia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Senegal</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/senegal</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Senegal. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/senegal</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/senegal/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Serbia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/serbia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Serbia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/serbia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/serbia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Seychelles</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/seychelles</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Seychelles. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/seychelles</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/seychelles/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sierra Leone</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sierra-leone</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sierra Leone. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sierra-leone</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sierra-leone/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Singapore</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/singapore</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Singapore. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/singapore</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/singapore/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sint Maarten</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sint-maarten</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sint Maarten. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sint-maarten</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/sint-maarten/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Slovakia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovakia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Slovakia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovakia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovakia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Slovenia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovenia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Slovenia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovenia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/slovenia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Somalia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/somalia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Somalia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/somalia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/somalia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for United Arab Emirates</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-arab-emirates</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in United Arab Emirates. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-arab-emirates</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-arab-emirates/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for the United States of America</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in the United States of America. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Uruguay</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uruguay</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Uruguay. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uruguay</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uruguay/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Uzbekistan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uzbekistan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Uzbekistan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uzbekistan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/uzbekistan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Venezuela</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/venezuela</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Venezuela. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/venezuela</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/venezuela/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Prince Edward Island (Canada Full)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/prince-edward-island</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Prince Edward Island. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada Full</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/prince-edward-island</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/prince-edward-island/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Yukon (Canada Full)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/yukon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Yukon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada Full</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/yukon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada-full/yukon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Alberta (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/alberta</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Alberta. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/alberta</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/alberta/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for British Columbia (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/british-columbia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in British Columbia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/british-columbia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/british-columbia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Manitoba (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/manitoba</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Manitoba. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/manitoba</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/manitoba/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for New Brunswick (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/new-brunswick</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in New Brunswick. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/new-brunswick</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/new-brunswick/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Newfoundland and Labrador (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/newfoundland-and-labrador</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Newfoundland and Labrador. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/newfoundland-and-labrador</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/newfoundland-and-labrador/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Northwest Territories (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/northwest-territories</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Northwest Territories. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/northwest-territories</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/northwest-territories/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nova Scotia (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nova-scotia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nova Scotia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nova-scotia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nova-scotia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nunavut (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nunavut</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nunavut. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nunavut</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/nunavut/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Ontario (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/ontario</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Ontario. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/ontario</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/ontario/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Prince Edward Island (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/prince-edward-island</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Prince Edward Island. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/prince-edward-island</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/prince-edward-island/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Quebec (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/quebec</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Quebec. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/quebec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/quebec/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Saskatchewan (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/saskatchewan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Saskatchewan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/saskatchewan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/saskatchewan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Yukon (Canada)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/yukon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Yukon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Canada</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/yukon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/canada/yukon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Amazonas (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/amazonas</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Amazonas. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/amazonas</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/amazonas/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Antioquia (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/antioquia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Antioquia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/antioquia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/antioquia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Arauca (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/arauca</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Arauca. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/arauca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/arauca/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Atlantico (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/atlantico</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Atlantico. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/atlantico</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/atlantico/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Bogota (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bogota</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Bogota. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bogota</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bogota/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Bolivar (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bolivar</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Bolivar. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bolivar</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/bolivar/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Boyaca (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/boyaca</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Boyaca. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/boyaca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/boyaca/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Caldas (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caldas</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Caldas. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caldas</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caldas/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Caqueta (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caqueta</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Caqueta. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caqueta</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/caqueta/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Baden-Württemberg (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/baden-württemberg</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Baden-Württemberg. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/baden-württemberg</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/baden-württemberg/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Bayern (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bayern</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Bayern. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bayern</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bayern/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Berlin (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/berlin</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Berlin. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/berlin</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/berlin/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Brandenburg (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/brandenburg</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Brandenburg. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/brandenburg</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/brandenburg/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Bremen (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bremen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Bremen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bremen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/bremen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hamburg (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hamburg</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hamburg. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hamburg</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hamburg/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hessen (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hessen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hessen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hessen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/hessen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mecklenburg-Vorpommern (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/mecklenburg-vorpommern</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mecklenburg-Vorpommern. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/mecklenburg-vorpommern</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/mecklenburg-vorpommern/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Niedersachsen (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/niedersachsen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Niedersachsen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/niedersachsen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/niedersachsen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nordrhein-Westfalen (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/nordrhein-westfalen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nordrhein-Westfalen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/nordrhein-westfalen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/nordrhein-westfalen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Rheinland-Pfalz (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/rheinland-pfalz</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Rheinland-Pfalz. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/rheinland-pfalz</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/rheinland-pfalz/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Saarland (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/saarland</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Saarland. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/saarland</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/saarland/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sachsen-Anhalt (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen-anhalt</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sachsen-Anhalt. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen-anhalt</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen-anhalt/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sachsen (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sachsen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/sachsen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Schleswig-Holstein (Germany)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/schleswig-holstein</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Schleswig-Holstein. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Germany</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/schleswig-holstein</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/germany/schleswig-holstein/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for West Bengal (India)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/west-bengal</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in West Bengal. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>India</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/west-bengal</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/west-bengal/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Abruzzo (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/abruzzo</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Abruzzo. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/abruzzo</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/abruzzo/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Basilicata (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/basilicata</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Basilicata. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/basilicata</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/basilicata/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Calabria (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/calabria</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Calabria. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/calabria</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/calabria/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Campania (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/campania</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Campania. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/campania</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/campania/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Emilia-Romagna (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/emilia-romagna</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Emilia-Romagna. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/emilia-romagna</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/emilia-romagna/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Friuli Venezia Giulia (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/friuli-venezia-giulia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Friuli Venezia Giulia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/friuli-venezia-giulia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/friuli-venezia-giulia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lazio (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lazio</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lazio. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lazio</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lazio/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Liguria (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/liguria</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Liguria. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/liguria</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/liguria/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lombardia (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lombardia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lombardia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lombardia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/lombardia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Marche (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/marche</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Marche. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/marche</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/marche/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Molise (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/molise</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Molise. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/molise</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/molise/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Piemonte (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/piemonte</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Piemonte. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/piemonte</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/piemonte/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Puglia (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/puglia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Puglia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/puglia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/puglia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sardegna (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sardegna</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sardegna. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sardegna</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sardegna/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Sicilia (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sicilia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Sicilia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sicilia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/sicilia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Toscana (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/toscana</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Toscana. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/toscana</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/toscana/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Trentino-Alto Adige (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/trentino-alto-adige</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Trentino-Alto Adige. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/trentino-alto-adige</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/trentino-alto-adige/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Umbria (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/umbria</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Umbria. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/umbria</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/umbria/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Veneto (Italy)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/veneto</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Veneto. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Italy</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/veneto</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/italy/veneto/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Adygea Republic (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/adygea-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Adygea Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/adygea-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/adygea-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Altai Krai (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-krai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Altai Krai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-krai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-krai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Altai Republic (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Altai Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/altai-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Amur Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/amur-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Amur Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/amur-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/amur-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Komi Republic (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/komi-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Komi Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/komi-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/komi-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kostroma Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kostroma-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kostroma Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kostroma-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kostroma-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Krasnodar Krai (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnodar-krai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Krasnodar Krai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnodar-krai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnodar-krai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Krasnoyarsk Krai (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnoyarsk-krai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Krasnoyarsk Krai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnoyarsk-krai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/krasnoyarsk-krai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kurgan Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kurgan-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kurgan Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kurgan-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kurgan-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kursk Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kursk-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kursk Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kursk-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/kursk-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Leningrad Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/leningrad-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Leningrad Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/leningrad-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/leningrad-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lipetsk Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/lipetsk-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lipetsk Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/lipetsk-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/lipetsk-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Magadan Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/magadan-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Magadan Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/magadan-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/magadan-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mari El Republic (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mari-el-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mari El Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mari-el-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mari-el-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mordovia Republic (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mordovia-republic</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mordovia Republic. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mordovia-republic</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/mordovia-republic/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Moscow Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/moscow-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Moscow Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/moscow-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/moscow-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Yamalo-Nenets Autonomous Okrug (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yamalo-nenets-autonomous-okrug</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Yamalo-Nenets Autonomous Okrug. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yamalo-nenets-autonomous-okrug</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yamalo-nenets-autonomous-okrug/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Yaroslavl Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yaroslavl-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Yaroslavl Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yaroslavl-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/yaroslavl-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Zabaykalsky Krai (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/zabaykalsky-krai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Zabaykalsky Krai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/zabaykalsky-krai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/zabaykalsky-krai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Eastern Cape (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/eastern-cape</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Eastern Cape. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/eastern-cape</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/eastern-cape/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Free State (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/free-state</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Free State. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/free-state</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/free-state/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Gauteng (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/gauteng</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Gauteng. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/gauteng</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/gauteng/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kwazulu-Natal (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/kwazulu-natal</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kwazulu-Natal. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/kwazulu-natal</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/kwazulu-natal/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Limpopo (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/limpopo</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Limpopo. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/limpopo</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/limpopo/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mpumalanga (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/mpumalanga</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mpumalanga. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/mpumalanga</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/mpumalanga/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for North-West (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/north-west</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in North-West. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/north-west</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/north-west/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Northern Cape (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/northern-cape</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Northern Cape. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/northern-cape</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/northern-cape/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Western Cape (South Africa)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/western-cape</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Western Cape. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>South Africa</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/western-cape</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/south-africa/western-cape/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Aberdeen City (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeen-city</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Aberdeen City. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeen-city</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeen-city/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Aberdeenshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeenshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Aberdeenshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeenshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/aberdeenshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Angus (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/angus</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Angus. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/angus</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/angus/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Antrim and Newtownabbey (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/antrim-and-newtownabbey</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Antrim and Newtownabbey. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/antrim-and-newtownabbey</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/antrim-and-newtownabbey/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Ards and North Down (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ards-and-north-down</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Ards and North Down. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ards-and-north-down</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ards-and-north-down/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Argyll and Bute (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/argyll-and-bute</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Argyll and Bute. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/argyll-and-bute</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/argyll-and-bute/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Armagh City, Banbridge and Craigavon (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/armagh-city,-banbridge-and-craigavon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Armagh City, Banbridge and Craigavon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/armagh-city,-banbridge-and-craigavon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/armagh-city,-banbridge-and-craigavon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Barking and Dagenham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barking-and-dagenham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Barking and Dagenham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barking-and-dagenham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barking-and-dagenham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Barnet (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnet</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Barnet. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnet/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Barnsley (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnsley</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Barnsley. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnsley</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/barnsley/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Bath and North East Somerset (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/bath-and-north-east-somerset</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Bath and North East Somerset. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/bath-and-north-east-somerset</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/bath-and-north-east-somerset/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cheshire West and Chester (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cheshire-west-and-chester</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cheshire West and Chester. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cheshire-west-and-chester</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cheshire-west-and-chester/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for City of Edinburgh (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/city-of-edinburgh</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in City of Edinburgh. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/city-of-edinburgh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/city-of-edinburgh/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Clackmannanshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/clackmannanshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Clackmannanshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/clackmannanshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/clackmannanshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Conwy (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/conwy</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Conwy. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/conwy</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/conwy/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cornwall and Isles of Scilly (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cornwall-and-isles-of-scilly</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cornwall and Isles of Scilly. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cornwall-and-isles-of-scilly</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cornwall-and-isles-of-scilly/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for County Durham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/county-durham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in County Durham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/county-durham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/county-durham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Coventry (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/coventry</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Coventry. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/coventry</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/coventry/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Croydon (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/croydon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Croydon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/croydon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/croydon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cumbria (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cumbria</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cumbria. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cumbria</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/cumbria/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Darlington (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/darlington</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Darlington. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/darlington</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/darlington/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Denbighshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/denbighshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Denbighshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/denbighshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/denbighshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Derby (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derby</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Derby. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derby</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derby/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Derbyshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derbyshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Derbyshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derbyshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derbyshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Derry City and Strabane (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derry-city-and-strabane</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Derry City and Strabane. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derry-city-and-strabane</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/derry-city-and-strabane/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Devon (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/devon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Devon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/devon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/devon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Doncaster (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/doncaster</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Doncaster. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/doncaster</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/doncaster/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dorset (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dorset</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dorset. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dorset</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dorset/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dudley (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dudley</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dudley. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dudley</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dudley/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dumfries and Galloway (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dumfries-and-galloway</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dumfries and Galloway. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dumfries-and-galloway</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dumfries-and-galloway/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dundee City (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dundee-city</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dundee City. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dundee-city</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/dundee-city/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Ealing (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ealing</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Ealing. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ealing</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/ealing/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for East Ayrshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-ayrshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in East Ayrshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-ayrshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-ayrshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for East Dunbartonshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-dunbartonshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in East Dunbartonshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-dunbartonshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-dunbartonshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for East Lothian (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-lothian</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in East Lothian. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-lothian</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/east-lothian/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hillingdon (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hillingdon</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hillingdon. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hillingdon</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hillingdon/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hounslow (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hounslow</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hounslow. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hounslow</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/hounslow/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Inverclyde (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/inverclyde</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Inverclyde. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/inverclyde</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/inverclyde/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Isle of Anglesey (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-anglesey</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Isle of Anglesey. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-anglesey</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-anglesey/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Isle of Wight (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-wight</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Isle of Wight. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-wight</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/isle-of-wight/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Islington (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/islington</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Islington. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/islington</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/islington/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kensington and Chelsea (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kensington-and-chelsea</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kensington and Chelsea. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kensington-and-chelsea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kensington-and-chelsea/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kent (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kent</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kent. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kent</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kent/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kingston upon Hull, City of (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-hull,-city-of</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kingston upon Hull, City of. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-hull,-city-of</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-hull,-city-of/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kingston upon Thames (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-thames</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kingston upon Thames. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-thames</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kingston-upon-thames/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kirklees (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kirklees</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kirklees. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kirklees</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/kirklees/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Knowsley (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/knowsley</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Knowsley. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/knowsley</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/knowsley/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lambeth (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lambeth</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lambeth. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lambeth</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lambeth/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lancashire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lancashire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lancashire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lancashire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lancashire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Leeds (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leeds</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Leeds. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leeds</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leeds/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Leicester (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicester</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Leicester. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicester</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicester/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Leicestershire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicestershire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Leicestershire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicestershire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/leicestershire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lewisham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lewisham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lewisham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lewisham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lewisham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lincolnshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lincolnshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lincolnshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lincolnshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lincolnshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Lisburn and Castlereagh (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lisburn-and-castlereagh</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Lisburn and Castlereagh. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lisburn-and-castlereagh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/lisburn-and-castlereagh/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Liverpool (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/liverpool</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Liverpool. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/liverpool</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/liverpool/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Luton (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/luton</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Luton. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/luton</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/luton/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Manchester (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/manchester</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Manchester. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/manchester</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/manchester/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Medway (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/medway</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Medway. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/medway</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/medway/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Oldham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oldham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Oldham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oldham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oldham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Orkney Islands (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/orkney-islands</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Orkney Islands. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/orkney-islands</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/orkney-islands/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Oxfordshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oxfordshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Oxfordshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oxfordshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/oxfordshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Pembrokeshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/pembrokeshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Pembrokeshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/pembrokeshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/pembrokeshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Perth and Kinross (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/perth-and-kinross</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Perth and Kinross. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/perth-and-kinross</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/perth-and-kinross/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Peterborough (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/peterborough</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Peterborough. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/peterborough</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/peterborough/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Plymouth (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/plymouth</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Plymouth. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/plymouth</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/plymouth/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Torfaen (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/torfaen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Torfaen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/torfaen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/torfaen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Tower Hamlets (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/tower-hamlets</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Tower Hamlets. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/tower-hamlets</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/tower-hamlets/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Trafford (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/trafford</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Trafford. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/trafford</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/trafford/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Vale of Glamorgan (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/vale-of-glamorgan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Vale of Glamorgan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/vale-of-glamorgan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/vale-of-glamorgan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wakefield (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wakefield</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wakefield. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wakefield</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wakefield/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Walsall (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/walsall</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Walsall. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/walsall</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/walsall/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Waltham Forest (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/waltham-forest</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Waltham Forest. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/waltham-forest</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/waltham-forest/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wandsworth (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wandsworth</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wandsworth. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wandsworth</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wandsworth/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Warrington (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warrington</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Warrington. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warrington</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warrington/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Warwickshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warwickshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Warwickshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warwickshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/warwickshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for West Berkshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-berkshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in West Berkshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-berkshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-berkshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for West Dunbartonshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-dunbartonshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in West Dunbartonshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-dunbartonshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-dunbartonshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for West Lothian (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-lothian</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in West Lothian. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-lothian</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-lothian/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for West Sussex (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-sussex</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in West Sussex. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-sussex</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/west-sussex/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Westminster (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/westminster</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Westminster. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/westminster</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/westminster/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wigan (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wigan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wigan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wigan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wigan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wiltshire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wiltshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wiltshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wiltshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wiltshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Windsor and Maidenhead (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/windsor-and-maidenhead</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Windsor and Maidenhead. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/windsor-and-maidenhead</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/windsor-and-maidenhead/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wirral (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wirral</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wirral. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wirral</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wirral/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wokingham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wokingham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wokingham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wokingham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wokingham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wolverhampton (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wolverhampton</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wolverhampton. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wolverhampton</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wolverhampton/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Worcestershire (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/worcestershire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Worcestershire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/worcestershire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/worcestershire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Wrexham (United Kingdom)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wrexham</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Wrexham. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wrexham</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-kingdom-local/wrexham/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Indiana (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/indiana</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Indiana. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/indiana</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/indiana/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Iowa (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/iowa</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Iowa. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/iowa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/iowa/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kansas (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kansas</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kansas. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kansas</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kansas/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kentucky (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kentucky</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kentucky. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kentucky</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/kentucky/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Louisiana (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/louisiana</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Louisiana. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/louisiana</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/louisiana/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Maine (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maine</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Maine. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maine</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maine/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Maryland (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maryland</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Maryland. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maryland</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/maryland/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Massachusetts (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/massachusetts</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Massachusetts. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/massachusetts</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/massachusetts/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Michigan (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/michigan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Michigan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/michigan</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/michigan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Minnesota (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/minnesota</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Minnesota. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/minnesota</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/minnesota/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mississippi (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/mississippi</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mississippi. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/mississippi</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/mississippi/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Missouri (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/missouri</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Missouri. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/missouri</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/missouri/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Montana (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/montana</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Montana. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/montana</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/montana/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nebraska (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nebraska</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nebraska. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nebraska</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nebraska/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nevada (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nevada</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nevada. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nevada</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/nevada/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for New Hampshire (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-hampshire</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in New Hampshire. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-hampshire</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-hampshire/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for New Jersey (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-jersey</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in New Jersey. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-jersey</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-jersey/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for New Mexico (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-mexico</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in New Mexico. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-mexico</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-mexico/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for New York (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-york</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in New York. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-york</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/new-york/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for North Carolina (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/north-carolina</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in North Carolina. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/north-carolina</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/north-carolina/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cantho (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/cantho</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cantho. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/cantho</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/cantho/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Caobang (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/caobang</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Caobang. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/caobang</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/caobang/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Daklak (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daklak</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Daklak. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daklak</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daklak/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Daknong (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daknong</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Daknong. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daknong</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/daknong/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Danang (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/danang</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Danang. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/danang</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/danang/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dienbien (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dienbien</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dienbien. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dienbien</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dienbien/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dongnai (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongnai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dongnai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongnai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongnai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Dongthap (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongthap</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Dongthap. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongthap</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/dongthap/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Gialai (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/gialai</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Gialai. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/gialai</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/gialai/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hagiang (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hagiang</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hagiang. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hagiang</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hagiang/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Haiduong (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiduong</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Haiduong. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiduong</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiduong/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Haiphong (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiphong</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Haiphong. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiphong</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haiphong/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hanam (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanam</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hanam. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanam</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanam/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hanoi (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanoi</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hanoi. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanoi</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hanoi/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hatinh (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hatinh</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hatinh. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hatinh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hatinh/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Haugiang (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haugiang</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Haugiang. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haugiang</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/haugiang/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hoabinh (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hoabinh</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hoabinh. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hoabinh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hoabinh/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hochiminh (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hochiminh</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hochiminh. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hochiminh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hochiminh/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Hungyen (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hungyen</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Hungyen. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hungyen</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/hungyen/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Khanhhoa (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/khanhhoa</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Khanhhoa. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/khanhhoa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/khanhhoa/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kiengiang (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kiengiang</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kiengiang. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kiengiang</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kiengiang/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Kontum (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kontum</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Kontum. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kontum</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/kontum/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Laichau (Vietnam)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/laichau</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Laichau. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Vietnam</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/laichau</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/vietnam/laichau/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Ulyanovsk Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/ulyanovsk-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Ulyanovsk Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/ulyanovsk-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/ulyanovsk-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Grenada</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/grenada</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Grenada. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/grenada</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/grenada/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Chile</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/chile</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Chile. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/chile</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/chile/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for South Carolina (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-carolina</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in South Carolina. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-carolina</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-carolina/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Casanare (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/casanare</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Casanare. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/casanare</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/casanare/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Vladimir Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vladimir-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Vladimir Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vladimir-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vladimir-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Guadeloupe</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guadeloupe</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Guadeloupe. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guadeloupe</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guadeloupe/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for China</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/china</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in China. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/china</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/china/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for South Dakota (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-dakota</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in South Dakota. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-dakota</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/south-dakota/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cauca (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cauca</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cauca. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cauca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cauca/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Volgograd Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/volgograd-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Volgograd Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/volgograd-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/volgograd-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Mizoram (India)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/mizoram</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Mizoram. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>India</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/mizoram</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/mizoram/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Guam</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guam</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Guam. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Oceania</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guam</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/guam/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Tennessee (United States)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/tennessee</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Tennessee. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>United States</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/tennessee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/united-states/tennessee/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Cesar (Colombia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cesar</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Cesar. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cesar</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/colombia/cesar/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Vologda Oblast (Russia)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vologda-oblast</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Vologda Oblast. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Russia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vologda-oblast</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/russia/vologda-oblast/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Colombia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Colombia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <category>Colombia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimates for Nagaland (India)</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/nagaland</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting in Nagaland. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>India</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/nagaland</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/subnational/india/nagaland/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for the United Kingdom</title>
      <dc:creator>Katharine Sherratt*, Sam Abbott*, Sophie R Meakin, Joel Hellewell, James D Munday, Nikos Bosse, CMMID Covid-19 working group, Mark Jit, Sebastian Funk</dc:creator>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in reporting both nationally and subnationally in the United Kingdom. Estimates using test positive cases are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively.</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <category>United Kingdom</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="3840" height="3840"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
tem>
  </channel>
</rss>
